This machine Sir Hi Good afternoon Baja
what is your view on the market and which are the best at this time
Martin is very bad and I
say that because inflation in
universities in which is the indicator
Champion Trophy ID number one is positive from the side also
this channel number and I think
insurance construction real estate so you
tell me the temple is visible and
starting and entertainment so please watch this
video the entry point is the price of 1525
take it and then cover 150 cm and a little
profit booking home
talk to my this price second buy I told
you yesterday also I like it very much at this price
whisky for ₹10 and a half and will be
10 strongest in the last important
so in 13-08-13 Norway's stoploss
target of 225 is absolutely fine so
where is Baja's temple I want to buy bearish I want to
buy Selva both the targets you guys on the screen